Encounters are mysterious! But cases are even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والقضايا تلفّها طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Today's case is a suspicious car! Be careful on the road!
!قضيّة اليوم تتمحور حول سيارة مشبوهة! احذر من حوادث الطريق
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Ayumi-chan! Mitsuhiko! Genta! Here we go!
!أيومي-تشان، ميتسوهيكو، غينتا! ها نحن
Roger, Conan-kun!
!عُلم يا كونان-كن
You can count on us!
!دع الأمر لنا
Let's do this thing!
!نحن مستعدّون
Take this!
!خُذ
Now!
!هيّا
W-What the...
!ما-ماذا؟
Let me down! Let me down from here!
!أنزلوني! أنزلوني الآن
The Junior Detective League...
...نصر كبير لفرقة
...is victorious!
!فتيان التحرّي
We'll take on any case!
!سنقبل بأيّ قضيّة
We'll investigate any case!
!ونحقّق فيها
And solve any case!
!ونحلّها
Hey, now.... you're bragging a little too much...
مهلكم... تبجّحكم كبير
You can count on the Junior Detective League!
!يمكنكم الاعتماد على فرقة فتيان التحرّي
Four Schoolchildren Catch Jewel Thief
أربعة طلّاب في الابتدائية يقبضون على لصّ مجوهرات
Thanks for the food!
!شكراً على الطعام
Geez, you guys ate a ton! Don't any of you know what constraint is?!
!يا إلهي، أنتم تأكلون بشراهة ألا تعرفون ضبط النفس؟
Go treat the kiddos to a meal or something, Mori-kun!
فلتعزم الصغار على وجبة أو ما شابه !مكافأةً لهم يا موري-كن
Me?!
!أنا؟
Bah. There goes all my spending money for this month.
تبّاً، تبخّر مصروف هذا الشهر تماماً
You're amazing! He was wanted for fifty different robberies!
كان ذلك مُبهراً، فاللصّ قد كان مطلوباً !لخمسين جريمة سطو
Conan-kun found him! He seemed suspicious in the jewelry shop!
وجده كونان-كن، فقد بدا مثيراً للشبهة في محلّ المجوهرات
It was just sheer luck, though.
كان ذلك بمحض المصادفة مع ذلك
Now we're gonna get even more clients!
!سنحصل على المزيد من العملاء هكذا
Yeah! We should get our own office!
!أجل! علينا تجهيز مكتبنا الخاص
Hey! A car's coming!
انتبهي، هناك سيّارة قادمة
Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان
Damn!
!تبّاً
"Shinjuku 33, NA 33-96!"
!شينجوكو 33، نا 33-96
A hit-and-run!
!اصطدام وهروب
Ran! You stay here! I'm going to get the police and an ambulance!
!ران، ابقي هنا! سأذهب للاتّصال بالإسعاف والشرطة
Look after her, Ran-neechan!
!اعتني بها يا ران-نيتشان
Don't say a word, Conan!
!لا تقل شيئاً يا كونان
We can't leave this entirely to the police!
!لا يمكننا ترك هذا الأمر للشرطة فحسب
Okay! Hold on tight!
!حسناً، تشبّثوا جيّداً
It turned!
!انعطفت
We're gonna lose it if we don't speed up!
!سنفقد أثرها إذا لم نسرع
I know!
!أعرف ذلك
There's the car!
!إنّها سيّارة الفاعل
I thought we lost it! Lucky!
!ظننتنا فقدنا أثرها! يا لحظّنا
It's stopped again!
!توقّفت مجدداً
It must have engine trouble!
!لا بدّ أنّها مشكلة بالمحرك
Talk about lucky!
!يا لحظّنا
It stops at every turn... Almost as if it's waiting for us!
...يتوقّف عند كلّ منعطف !كما لو أنّه ينتظر لحاقنا به
There it goes!
!إنّه يهرب
Hey! What're you doing, Conan?! Go faster!
!ما الذي تفعله يا كونان؟ أسرع أكثر
I don't see the car...
...لا أرى السيّارة
Did it finally lose us?
هل فقدنا أثرها أخيراً؟
Look for it!
!لنبحث عنها
Right!
!أجل
Hey! Is it hidden in here?!
لحظة، أيمكن أنّها مخبّأة هنا؟
No, there's no place for it.
كلا، لا مكان لها
Plus, it looks like this factory is closed today.
كما يبدو أنّ هذا المصنع مغلقٌ اليوم
Ishikura Industries
إيشيكورا للصناعات
Let's check around back!
!لنتفقّد في الخلف
What a bad road! There's no pavement here!
!يا للطريق السيّئّ! لا ترصيف هنا
There are stairs this way. Which means...!
...توجد أدراج في هذا الاتّجاه، مما يعني
I don't see anything.
ليست موجودة
There's a cigarette shop! Let's ask there!
!يوجد محلّ سجائر هناك! لنسألهم
Lady! Did a red car just pass by here?!
يا جدّة، أمرّت سيّارة حمراء قبل قليل؟
I'm not sure. A couple cars did pass by, but...
لا أدري، مرّت سيّارتان إلى ثلاثة لكنّي لست واثقة
It's a two-door!
!إنّها ثنائيّة الباب
And a sports car!
!سيّارة رياضية
I don't know anything about cars...
لا أفقه في السيّارات كثيراً
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Oh, it's you! How're you doing?
أنت إذاً! كيف حالك؟
Hey, we've been here three minutes now.
مرّت ثلاث دقائق مذ أتينا هنا
The person is long gone by now...
لعلّه هرب الآن على الأرجح
Damn!
!تبّاً
Look there!
!انظروا هناك
A red car! That's it!
!سيّارة حمراء! تلك هي
Its engine stalled again! We're lucky!
!محرّكها توقّف مُجدداً! الحظّ معنا
No! It's different from before! It wasn't there earlier!
،كلا، هذا مختلف عن السابق !فلم تكن توجد سيّارة هناك قبل قليل
Did it back up or something?! What for?!
هل رجع؟ لمَ؟
We got it this time!
!سنمسك به هذه المرّة
There's no escape!
!لن تهرب
Alright! We got it! Just a little more!
!حسنٌ، ممتاز! بقي القليل فقط
Oww...
...مؤلم
Beika Local Police Station
مركز شرطة بيكا المحليّ
T-This is...
...هـ-هذا
...a police station...
مركز شرطة؟
Officer, please arrest me. I committed a hit-and-run.
!حضرة الضابط، فلتعتقلني رجاءً فقد أقدمت على جريمة اصطدام وهرب
H-He's turning himself in?
يـ-يسلّم نفسه؟
Beika Central Hospital
مشفى بيكا المركزيّ
He tried to run away after he hit you,
،حاول الهرب بعد اصطدامه بك
but he decided to turn himself in after the guilt got to him.
لكنّه قرّر تسليم نفسه بعدما أنّبه ضميره
Geez! How anti-climatic!
!يا إلهي، يا للنهاية المُثبطة
I wanted the Junior Detective League to use more of its might!
أردتُ أن تستعمل فرقة فتيان !التحرّي قوّتها أكثر
What's wrong, Conan-kun?
ما الخطب يا كونان-كن؟
Oh, nothing.
لا شيء
So, how is Ayumi?
بأيّ حال، كيف هي أيومي؟
She only got some scratches, thankfully.
كانت إصاباتها خفيفة لحسن الحظّ
They said she doesn't need to be hospitalized.
قالوا أنّ لا حاجة لتنويمها هنا
Then you can go home today!
!أي يمكنك العودة اليوم
That's great news!
!هذا رائع
No, it isn't. I lost the Detective League badge Conan-kun gave me.
ليس رائعاً، فقدت شارة فرقة فتيان التحرّي التي أعطاني إيّاها كونان-كن
You dropped it when you were hit?
سقطت منك عندما اصطدم بك؟
The policeman said they didn't see it.
سألت أحد رجال الشرطة، وقال أنّهم لم يروها
Don't worry! I can have the Doc make another one!
لا تقلقي، سأطلب من البروفسور صنع بديلة
Really?! I'm so happy! That's why I like you, Conan-kun!
!حقّاً؟ هذا يسعدني! لذا أحبّك يا كونان-كن
That's not fair, Conan.
هذا دنيءٌ يا كونان
Buying her love with objects... You coward!
!تشتري حبّها بماديّات... أيّها الجبان
Oh, geez...
...أنتما
Hey, you kids! Come with me to the factory on 4th Street!
اسمعوا، عليكم مرافقتي للمصنع في الشارع الرابع فوراً
The inspector is waiting!
فالمفتّش في انتظارنا
The factory on 4th Street? That's the place we passed by earlier.
المصنع في الشارع الرابع؟ إنّه المكان الذي مررنا به قبل قليل
Did something happen?
أحصل شيءٌ يا عمّ؟
Someone died there. It was apparently a murder.
،مات أحدهم في ذاك المصنع ويبدو أنّها جريمة قتل
Listen! You kids stay here!
اسمعوا، عليكم البقاء هنا
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
Oh, you came!
أتيت إذاً؟
Getting right to the point, here's the situation.
سأدخل في صلب الموضوع، هذا هو الوضع
President of Ishikura Industries, Ishikura Hisashi (50)
رئيس إيشيكورا للصناعات (إيشيكورا هيساشي (50
The victim was the president of this factory,
،كان الضحيّة هو رئيس هذا المصنع
lshikura Hisashi-san, age 50.
إيشيكورا هيساشي-سان، 50 عاماً
This was a robbery.
هذه جريمة سطو
Yes, we're investigating it as a robbery murder.
أجل، نحن نحقّق على أساس كونها جريمة سطو وقتل
The factory is closed today,
المصنع مغلقٌ اليوم
but Ishikura-san was apparently here alone, checking the products.
لكن أتى إيشيكورا-سان بمفرده لتفقّد المنتجات وفقما يبدو
There are tape marks on his mouth and wrist.
توجد آثار شريط لاصق على فمه ومعصمه
Meaning he was strangled.
مما يعني أنّه كان مقيّداً
But why bother removing the tape? The killer--
...لكن لمَ نُزع الشريط؟ ما الذي أراده القاتل
Quit scampering around the scene!
!لا تتجوّل في مسرح الجريمة
I'm sorry!
!آسف
The back door is diagonal from the cigarette lady's shop...
الباب الخلفيّ يقابل متجر ...السجائر للجدّة بشكل قطري
We'll have to wait for the autopsy for details,
،علينا انتظار نتائج التشريح للتفاصيل
but he died approximately an hour ago.
لكن وقت الوفاة المقدّر هو قبل قرابة ساعة
That's the same time we passed by here!
!كنّا قد مررنا هنا قبل ساعة
No question about it!
!لا شكّ في الأمر
I thought so!
!كما ظننت
Did you see anyone suspicious then?!
هل رأيتم شخصاً مثيراً للشبهة وقتها؟
No, not really...
...بصراحة، في ذاك الوقت
We were focused on following the hit-and-run man...
كنّا منشغلين بملاحقة السائق ...الذي اصطدم وهرب
Oh! That's him!
!أ-أليس هذا هو؟
See?! The guy in the back, near the middle!
!انظر! الشخص الذي يقف في المنتصف خلفاً
Oh! He's the one who hit Ayumi-chan!
!إنّه الرجل الذي اصطدم بأيومي-تشان
What now?!
!ماذا؟
Are you sure?!
أأنتم متأكّدون؟
We're certain of it!
!لا شكّ بالأمر
I bet he did this murder, too!
!لعلّه من ارتكب جريمة القتل أيضاً
Yeah, right! It's just coincidence!
!مستحيل، كانت مصادفة
Obviously!
!بالتأكيد
Who'd commit a robbery murder while running from a hit-and-run?!
فمن يقدم على سطو وقتل !وهو يهرب من حادثة اصطدام مروري؟
Beika Police Department
مركز شرطة بيكا
Former Ishikura Ind., Employee Shishido Kenichi (35)
موظّف سابق في إيشيكورا للصناعات (شيشيدو كينيتشي (35
The children started chasing me,
بدأ الأطفال بملاحقتي
and my car stalled on the curve a little ways behind the factory.
وتوقّفت سيّارتي عند المنعطف وراء المصنع بقليل
I never stopped the car behind the factory, nor did I murder anyone.
لم أوقف السيّارة وراءه
It's just coincidence...
...كانت محض مصادفة
He used to work at that factory, and was let go due to his misconduct.
،إنّه موظّف سابق في ذاك المصنع وتمّ فصله لسوء سلوكه الشهر الفائت
Inspector! You don't think...
...أ-أيمكن يا سيّدي المفتّش أنّه
He really did do it?!
!كان الفاعل حقّاً؟
He couldn't have, Genta-kun!
ذلك مستحيل يا غينتا-كن
Why's that?
لمَ؟
We were in front of the factory when it happened!
كنّا أمام المصنع في ذاك الوقت
But, Inspector!
،لكن سيّدي المفتّش
He could've used the back door while he was out of the kids' sight!
كان بإمكانه الدخول من الباب الخلفيّ !بعدما توارى عن أنظار الأطفال
Yes, but we spoke with the cigarette shop lady behind the factory.
لكنّنا سألنا جدّة متجر السجائر أمام الباب الخلفيّ للمصنع
No cars stopped near here. Not behind the factory or on the street.
،لم تتوقّف أيّ سيّارة بالقرب من هنا لا وراء المصنع ولا على الشارع
Location of car Ishikura Industries
متجرها يقابل باب المصنع الخلفيّ
Her shop is right across from the factory's back entrance.
محلّ السجائر
Cigarette shop Conan and friends
فيمكننا الوثوق بشهادتها
Which would mean it really was just coincidence...
...مما يعني أنّها كانت محض مصادفة بالفعل
No! There's another side to these two incidents!
!كلا، يوجد جانب آخر لهاتين القضيّتين
Something big that we haven't noticed yet!
!شيء كبير لم نلحظه بعد
Is there still something else, Conan?
لا يزال هناك شيءٌ يا كونان؟
Come on, let's go visit Ayumi-chan!
!لنذهب لزيارة أيومي-تشان
You guys go on ahead.
فلتسبقاني
No! The Junior Detective League must always work as a team!
كلا! على فرقة فتيان التحرّي أن !تلتزم بالعمل الجماعيّ دوماً
But I need juice first. I'm thirsty.
لكنّي أريد عصيراً قبل ذلك، فأشعر بالعطش
There's some juice over there! By the cigarette shop!
!يوجد عصير هناك، بجوار محلّ السجائر
Oh, Wataru did? He was such a studious boy, too...
...حقّاً؟ فعل واتارو ذلك؟ مع أنّه كان صبيّاً مجتهداً
Wait a minute!
!انتظر
Say, lady!
أخبريني يا جدّة
When the factory incident happened, did anyone call you by mistake?
هل أتاكِ اتّصال خاطئ عندما وقعت الحادثة في المصنع؟
Just as I thought! As I recall, that alleyway had--
...كما ظننت! وفقما أذكر، فقد كان في الزقاق
Thanks, lady! Bye!
!شكراً لك يا جدّة! إلى اللقاء
What's going on, Conan?
ما الخطب يا كونان؟
Genta! Lift me up on your shoulders!
!غينتا! ارفعني على كتفيك
Lift you up?
يرفعك؟
Is there something in there?
أيوجد شيءٌ هناك؟
I knew it!
!بالفعل
It's just as I thought!
!كما ظننت
What's that?!
...ذلك
Aha! That's where it is!
!فهمت! كان هنا
Say what?! Shishido Kenichi, the hit-and-run guy?!
ماذا؟! شيشيدو كينيتشي، مُرتكب الاصطدام والهرب نفسه؟
Alright! Got it, Mori-kun!
!أجل، فهمت يا موري-كن
Okay! Now for the old guy!
حسناً، دور العمّ
Mori-kun? This is Megure.
موري-كن؟ أنا ميغوري
Could you hurry down to the factory on 4th Street?
هلّا أتيت للمصنع على الشارع الرابع بشكلٍ عاجل؟
Good work.
بُوركت جهودكما
Where are you, Inspector?
حضرة المفتّش، أين أنت؟
We've been expecting you!
!كنّا بانتظارك
H-Hey, you! What are you doing here?!
!أ-أنتما! ما الذي تفعلانه هنا؟
Inspector Megure will be here shortly!
سيأتي المفتّش ميغوري قريباً
Please wait here until then!
انتظر هنا من فضلك
Oh, you can be considerate! Don't mind if I do...
تتحلّيان بالأخلاق، لا أمانع فعل ذلك إذاً
I wish I could've had at least one sip first...
أتمنّى لو أني استطعت ارتشاف ...رشفة واحدة على الأقل قبلها
It's just like Conan said...
كما قال كونان
He became Sleeping Kogoro the instant he entered the crime scene!
!يصبح كوغورو النائم عندما يدخل مسرح جريمة
Didn't even notice we just filled an empty can with water!
!لم ينتبه لأنّنا ملأنا العلبة الفارغة بماء حتّى
Hey, Conan! Where are you?
كونان! أين أنت؟
What do we do next?
ماذا نفعل تالياً؟
Conan told me everything. I'll handle things from here.
أخبرني كونان بكلّ شيء، سأتولّى الموضوع من هنا
You can't be serious, old guy!
!لا يصحّ ذلك يا عمّ
Don't worry. I've made sure you'll be in the spotlight, too.
لا تقلقا، جهّزتُ دوراً لكما
Alright!
!رائع
Okay, then!
!حسناً إذاً
I brought him, Mori-kun.
موري-كن، جلبته معي
What is this about?
ما الأمر بالضبط؟
Shishido-san can answer that.
يعرف شيشيدو-سان تفاصيل ذلك تماماً
How is that?
ما قصدك؟
Today, you hit a little girl and drove off.
اصطدمت بفتاةٍ صغيرة اليوم وهربت
You then continued to drive, with those children in pursuit,
ثمّ واصلت القيادة ومجموعة الأطفال تلاحقك
and came by here...
ومررت بهذا المكان
...by this factory owned by Ishikura-san, whom you know and hate.
المصنع الذي يخصّ إيشيكورا-سان الذي تعرفه، بل تكنّ الضغينة له
Again, what are you talking about?
كما قلت، ما الأمر بالضبط؟
Oh? So you want me to say it, after all?
ماذا؟ تريدني أن أبوح أنا إذاً؟
Ishikura-san's killer was you, Shishido-san!
!قاتل إيشيكورا-سان كان أنت يا شيشيدو-سان
Hey, now! What are you saying?!
!مهلك! ما الذي تقوله؟
He was deemed innocent for the murder, at the very least!
!تمّت تبرئته، من جريمة القتل على الأقل
Yes.
أجل
It was believed that he couldn't have committed it while fleeing,
ظُنّ أنّ ارتكاب الجريمة بينما يلوذ بالفرار أمرٌ مستحيل
so he was cleared of all suspicion.
فزالت الشبهات المحيطة به
Yeah! You even have someone to vouch for me!
!صحيح! لديكم شهود حتّى
The kids who chased me!
!الصغار الذين لاحقوني
But what if that was planned?
لكن ماذا لو كان ذلك سابق التدبير؟
What if you intended for these children, the Junior Detective League,
،ماذا لو نويت أن يشهد لك هؤلاء الصغار
to act as witnesses for you?
فرقة فتيان التحرّي؟
W-What?! What do you mean?!
ما-ماذا؟! ما قصدك؟
In short, what if Ayumi-kun's hit-and-run incident
أي ماذا لو كانت حادثة الاصطدام والهرب المتعلّقة بأيومي-كن
had been meant to camouflage the murder?
تمويهاً لإخفاء الجريمة؟
Y-You can't be serious! Is that possible?!
لا-لا يُعقل! أكان بإمكانه ذلك؟
According to Conan, the car would unnaturally stop at each turn,
وفقاً لكونان، فقد كانت السيّارة تتوقّف عند كلّ منعطف بشكلٍ غريب
so they never lost sight of it.
فلم يفقدوا أثرها
If he was doing this so they could follow him, that would explain it.
لو كان يتعمّد ذلك كي يستطيعوا اللحاق به، فسيتوضّح كلّ شيء
My car really was in bad shape!
!كانت السيّارة بحالة سيّئة حقّاً
He's right, Mori-kun.
صحيح يا موري-كن
The car's spark plugs were worn and its engine was in bad condition.
،فقد كانت شمعة الاحتراق للسيّارة مهترئة ومحرّكها في حالة متردّية
Even an amateur could set that up, Inspector.
يمكن حتّى لمجّرد هاوٍ تدبير ذلك حضرة المفتّش
Okay, then. Even if that were the case, I have an alibi. A perfect one.
لا بأس، إذا كان الأمر كذلك فلديّ حجّة غياب، حجّة لا تشوبها شائبة
Yes. Aside from the three minutes the kids had lost sight of you.
أجل، باستثناء الثلاث دقائق التي فقد الصغار أثرك فيها
You can't do anything in three minutes.
لا يمكنك فعل شيء في ثلاث دقائق
No, it would've been more than enough to enter here.
كلا، بل هي كافية للدخول هنا
Ridiculous!
!سخافة
The cigarette lady would've seen my car stopped by the back door!
كانت جدّة محلّ السجائر لتنتبه لسيّارتي !لو أوقفتها عند الباب الخلفيّ
Oh? You know quite a lot...
عجباً، تعرف ذلك أيضاً
I worked here. It's only natural that I know.
كنتُ أعمل هنا، فمن الطبيعيّ أن أعرف
Then you must naturally know that shop's phone number, too.
لا بدّ أنّ من الطبيعيّ معرفتك برقم هاتف ذاك المحلّ أيضاً إذاً
I don't know what you're getting at.
لا-لا أفهم ما الذي تلمّح له
You couldn't stop the car by the back door. You walked here.
لم توقف السيّارة عند الباب الخلفيّ، بل أتيت مشياً
Then what about the car? How did it disappear?
ماذا عن السيّارة إذاً؟ أين وضعها؟
Conan!
!كونان
Right!
!حسناً
Where were you?!
!أين كنت؟
Never mind that!
،لا تهتموا لذلك
Show the inspector to the warehouse you lifted me up to look into!
فلترشدوا المفتّش ومن معه للمخزن !الذي اختلست النظر له
To that warehouse?
لذاك المخزن؟
T-This car!
!هـ-هذه السيّارة
It's the same as the hit-and-run car!
!إنّها نفس سيّارة الاصطدام والهرب
The number matches exactly, too!
!رقم اللوحة مطابق أيضاً
Shishido-san.
،شيشيدو-سان
Why does a car exactly like the hit-and run car exist here?!
لمَ توجد سيّارة مطابقة للسيّارة في حادثة الاصطدام والهرب؟
I don't know!
!لا أعرف
He probably modified a stolen car.
لعلّه قام بتعديل سيّارة مسروقة على الأرجح
You worked at a sheet metal and painting factory, Shishido-san.
كنت تعمل في مصنع صفائح معدنية وطلاء يا شيشيدو-سان
It would've been simple for you.
يُفترض أنّ الأمر كان بسيطاً عليك
First, you knocked Ishikura-san out with a sedative or something,
أفقدتَ إيشيكورا-سان وعيه أوّلاً بمنوّم أو ما شابه في مكتب المصنع
then tied him up with tape and left him there.
ثمّ قيّدته بشريط لاصق وتركته
You then took the modified car and committed the hit-and-run.
وأخذت السيّارة المعدّلة وارتكبت حادثة الاصطدام والهرب
You stopped the car occasionally so the children could follow you,
أوقفت السيّارة على فترات متقطّعة كي يستطيع الصغار اللحاق بك
eventually leading them to the factory,
وقدتهم لمقدمة المصنع بنهاية المطاف
Factory Office Cigarette Shop
وأخفيت السيّارة في المخزن
after which you hid the car in the warehouse.
المصنع
Next, you called the cigarette lady on your cell phone,
تالياً، اتّصلت بجدّة محلّ السجائر بهاتفك الخلويّ
passed by while her back was to the road,
ومررت أمامها بينما كان ظهرها للشارع
and entered the office through the back door.
ودخلت المكتب من الباب الخلفيّ
You quickly murdered Ishikura-san, removed the tape,
قتلت إيشيكورا-سان سريعاً واسترجعتَ الشريط اللاصق
and made it look like a robbery murder.
وجعلتها تبدو جريمة سطو وقتل
The safe was probably put in disarray in advance.
أثرتَ الفوضى في الخزنة سلفاً على الأرجح
When leaving the office, you called the cigarette shop lady again.
عند مغادرتك للمكتب، اتّصلت بجدّة محلّ السجائر مُجدداً
You then hurried to the other hidden car, took it out,
وأسرعت للسيّارة المخبّأة الأخرى، وأخرجتها
and waited for the children at the turn.
السيّارة المخبّأة
Of course, this one was your real car with your real license plate,
كانت تلك سيّارتك الحقيقيّة بلوحة الأرقام الأصليّة بالطبع
that you had tinkered with in advance to be in bad shape.
والتي قد تلاعبت بها كي تكون في حالٍ سيّئة سلفاً
R-Really?!
!حـ-حقّاً ذلك؟
How shocking!
!يا للصدمة
I've heard enough! My car was taken in after the hit-and-run!
لا تعبث معي! السيّارة التي اصطدمت بها !هي نفسها التي اُحتجزت
What proof do you have otherwise?!
!ما دليلك على خلاف ذلك؟
Detective Takagi. Was there any mud on the car taken into custody?
أيّها الضابط تاكاغي، أكان هناك وحل على السيّارة المحتجزة؟
Mud?
وحل؟
No, it was as clean as a new car.
كلا، كانت نظيفةً كسيّارة جديدة
There are mud puddles next to the factory.
كانت هناك بركة وحل بجوار المصنع
If a car passed through there, mud would splatter onto its body.
لو عبرت سيّارة هناك، فيُفترض أنّه تناثر عليها
Hey, you! Is there any mud on that car?!
أنت! أيوجد أيّ وحل على تلك السيّارة؟
What does that matter?! The mud came off my car while driving!
كأنّي أعرف علاقة ذلك! زال الوحل !من سيّارتي أثناء القيادة
Detective! If you're claiming that's the hit-and-run car, then prove it!
أيّها المتحرّي! إذا كنتَ تدّعي أنّ هذه هي السيّارة المستعملة في حادثة الاصطدام، فلتثبت ذلك
Very well.
حسنٌ
Conan!
!كونان
Hey, Mitsuhiko! Call Ayumi-chan with your badge!
!ميتسوهيكو! فلتتّصل على أيومي-تشان بشارتك
With my badge? But she lost hers!
بالشارة؟ لكنّها فقدت شارتها
Just call her!
لا يهمّ، اتّصل بها فحسب
Okay...
...حسناً
Hello? Ayumi-chan? Do you read me?
مرحباً؟ أيومي-تشان؟ أتستطيعين سماعي؟
Respond if you do. This is Mitsuhiko. How are you feeling?
أجيبي إن كنتِ كذلك، أنا ميتسوهيكو! كيف حالك؟
We'll come visit you later!
سنأتي لزيارتك لاحقاً
Inspector! I found this badge on the car!
!سيّدي المفتّش! وجدتُ هذه الشارة على السيّارة
What?!
ماذا؟
T-That's--!
...تـ-تلك
It's Ayumi's badge!
!إنّها شارة أيومي
It fell out of her pocket and got stuck to it during the hit-and-run!
سقطت من جيبها وعلقت بالسيّارة !بعد حادثة الاصطدام
You intended to use us for your alibi,
،نويت استغلالنا لبناء حجّة غيابك
but it seems we wound up proving your guilt instead.
لكنّها هُدمت وكشفت عن ذنبك بالمقابل
N-No! T-This can't be happening!
!مـ-مستحيل! لا يُعقل هذا
Here, Ayumi-chan! I found your badge!
هاك يا أيومي-تشان، وجدنا شارتك
Thank you, Conan-kun!
!شكراً لك يا كونان-كن
Conan-kun...
...كونان-كن
That's not fair...
كيف لك هذا؟
Hey! Conan! Where did she kiss you?!
!أنت! كونان! أين قبّلتك؟
Let us kiss you there!
!دعنا نقبّلك هناك
Huh? It's unlocked...
ماذا؟ إنّه غير مقفل
What a careless household...
...يا للمنزل المهمل
A blackout?
انقطاع تيّار؟
There's a pinprick on her back!
!أثر طعن على ظهرها
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Cooking Classroom Murder Case (Part 1)."
جريمة قتل فصل الطهو الدراسيّ (الجزء الأوّل)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Ice.
جليد
Next episode we attend a cooking class.
قضيّة الحلقة القادمة في !فصل طهو دراسيّ
Now add some pepper to the dish.
...ثم نضيف رشّة فلفل